var questions = [
  {
    num: 1,
    question: "1: What is JavaScript?",
    answer:
      "JavaScript is a programming language that enables interactive web pages.",
    Option: [
      "A style sheet language",
      "A markup language",
      "A scripting language",
      "A programming language that enables interactive web pages.",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 2,
    question: "2: What is the syntax for declaring a variable in JavaScript?",
    answer: "var variableName;",
    Option: [
      "variable variableName;",
      "v variableName;",
      "variableName = value;",
      "var variableName;",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 3,
    question:
      "3: What is the output of the following code: console.log(2 + '2' - 1);",
    answer: "21",
    Option: ["23", "221", "21", "NaN"],
  },
  {
    num: 4,
    question: "4: How do you write a comment in JavaScript?",
    answer: "// This is a comment",
    Option: [
      "' This is a comment",
      "<!-- This is a comment -->",
      "// This is a comment",
      "/* This is a comment */",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 5,
    question:
      "5: Which function is used to parse a string to an integer in JavaScript?",
    answer: "parseInt()",
    Option: ["intParse()", "parseString()", "stringToInt()", "parseInt()"],
  },
  {
    num: 6,
    question: "6: What does the '===â€‹' operator do in JavaScript?",
    answer: "Strict equality (checks both value and type)",
    Option: [
      "Assigns a value",
      "Equality (checks only value)",
      "Strict equality (checks both value and type)",
      "Not equal",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 7,
    question: "7: How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
    answer: "function myFunction() {}",
    Option: [
      "function = myFunction() {}",
      "create function myFunction() {}",
      "function: myFunction() {}",
      "function myFunction() {}",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 8,
    question: "8: What does the 'typeof' operator do in JavaScript?",
    answer: "Returns the data type of its operand",
    Option: [
      "Checks if a variable is defined",
      "Returns the data type of its operand",
      "Compares two variables",
      "Converts a string to a number",
    ],
  },
  {
    num: 9,
    question:
      "9: Which method is used to add a new element to an array in JavaScript?",
    answer: "push()",
    Option: ["addElement()", "append()", "push()", "insert()"],
  },
  {
    num: 10,
    question: "10: What does the 'this' keyword refer to in JavaScript?",
    answer: "Refers to the object it belongs to",
    Option: [
      "Refers to the previous object",
      "Refers to the global object",
      "Refers to the object it belongs to",
      "Refers to the parent object",
    ],
  },
];
